(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-07-26T21:53:57.233642",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon.
Attention For Visitors
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon.
Attention For Visitors
Greetings, CC, my fated rival.
Greetings, CC, my most distant rival!
And hello to every...
Everyone watching from...
Serendipity!
Woo!
Remember, if you want a chance for your wish to be featured on the Otomo or the Tako-dachi that we made...
Post about it with hashtag WishUponTakoTomo!
Yay! Thank you amiami for supporting our rivalry...
...and for supporting Serendipity!
Be sure to check out their booth at...
Anime Expo!
Yay! Yay!
[hololive BASE on Tour! 2026 Duet Stage!]
Hey pebbles!
It's Koseki Bijou!
Pebble!
And all of hololive BASE is here with me, all 14 of us!
hololive BASE is coming to Round 1 USA locations nationwide starting this September!
Come hang out with us!
Follow @round1usa on Instagram and X so you don't miss out on any updates!
We can't wait to see you there!
Bye-bye!
[The concert will be starting soon.]
[Attention For Visitors]
[2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales]
[Acrylic Stand / Keychain / Sticker]
[Button Badge / Acrylic Panel]
[hololive English 4th Concert: Serendipity]
[The concert will be starting soon.]
Attention For Visitors
2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales
hololive English 4th Concert - Serendipity
hololive English 4th Concert: Serendipity
The concert will be starting soon. / 開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon.
Attention For Visitors
2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales
The concert will be starting soon. 開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon. Please wait a moment until the performance begins.
Attention For Visitors
LastWrites
(Shiori Novella / Mori Calliope)
AutoFister
(Gigi Murin / Cecilia Immergreen)
BloodRaven
(Elizabeth Rose Bloodflame / Nerissa Ravencroft)
A-D-V-E-N-T
Everyone, let's wake it up!
Time to get this party started
Fire, fire, light the fire
Fire, higher, as you desire
Chasing what we aspire
Sparking up like wildfire
Never ever have I ever
Been a sinner, been a dreamer
Take the chance and with my lighter
Start the fire
Don't burn me out
I know the secret
It's overkiller, sad stories wearing me down
Snap out of the system
Break out, give it everything
This is our time
We're ready to start
Hello brand new world
Would you welcome the light?
And free us from the night
Fire, fire, light the fire
Higher, higher, as you desire
Igniting our hearts
Jump into the stream of light
新しい世界へ
To a brand new world
Jump into the end of time
次元の向こう側連れてってあげる
Let me take you to the other side of the dimension
Rebellion
I know that I can still be
The future of this story
I know that I can be free
The one and the only
They tell me that I'm crazy
I'll never let them stop me
With this our epic
Time to get this party started
Never ever have I ever
Been a sinner, been a dreamer
Fire, fire, light the fire
Igniting our hearts
Jump into the stream of light
新しい世界へ
To a brand new world
Jump into the end of time
次元の向こう側連れてってあげる
Let me take you to the other side of the dimension
Rebellion
Jump into the stream of light
それぞれのステージへ
To our respective stages
Jump into the end of time
奇跡の向こう側連れてってあげる
Let me take you to the other side of the miracle
Rebellion
Time to get this party started
Fire, fire, light the fire
Fire, higher, as you desire
Time to get this party started
Don't don't know me, unpredictable
Takin' you all below
Don't don't know me, irresistible
Takin' you all below, below we go
They think they want it, huh?
They wanna get, get, get some
We take them down, down, down
Right on the border line
Runnin' it's no surprise
You ain't gonna win, but you can try
I told you, you're no match
Step up inside my line-up
Listen, listen
Run and hide and scream out, already locked you out
Those games you always play
Call me, cover up, won't hear anything
Aiming to strike
Right on your heart
Throwing away the key, there's no night, night, night
Jump!
Live on...
...the edge
Running on the edge
Don't don't know me, unpredictable
Dipping to the low
Then let it all go
Don't you start to run
My love
No, you'll never know, never know what's up
Run in the light of my video
What's wrong, what's right with you?
Rushing in the fantasy
Under the disease
Sure that you will never make it out
Eyes on us now, do it, do it
Instant regret, make 'em kneel, kneel, kneel
Enemies gonna lose count, oh!
Free your guilty...
...heart
We are not gonna stop, it's just...
...our start!
Get down, get down, run the track
Running like that, running like that
Get down!
Get down, down, down, down
And let go
Takin' you all below
Don't you already know?
Don't you already know it?
Run in the light of my video
What's wrong, what's right with you?
Run in the night of my video
Come take a bite
Never-ending underworld!
Justice, just like that
Justice, get, get that
We rise
Standing on the edge, don't know me, unpredictable, typical you
Got nowhere to go
Show you something real, my level, no you'll never know
As above so below, you should know
So let's go
Just a little unpredictable, beautiful
Just the start, let's get it, let's get 'em baby
Go, next level, almost criminal
As above so it goes below
준비
Get ready
다스려진 머리 what a shame
Ruled mind, what a shame
Player들은 다 complain
Players all complain
Why me? No, 너나 나나 똑같이
Why me? No, you and I are both the same
Shout out, 따따따!
Shout out, louder!
익숙해진 타임, so try to dive
Accustomed time, so try to dive
Look around, 넌 만족하니?
Look around, are you satisfied?
The broken and bruised, I got something to prove now
Abracadabra, let's go!
움직여 봐, 다 쓰러져
Move, they all fall down
끝까지 가보는 거야
We're going all the way to the end
나를 흔들어 대
They shake me up
Double, double, double, let it, let it, let it down
We hit that high
Snake, snake, snake, come on now, don't be shy
Snake, snake, snake
뜨겁게 달아올라
Burning up hot
너와 나 어때, all day, all night
How about you and me, all day, all night
Don't turn it off, can't stop, won't stop reaching
Who said the sky's the limit?
Show them that we mean business
We are the young ambitious
세계는 절대 거짓말 안 해
The world never lies
Fly high with pride and leave your fears behind
지켜봐, 우린 이 판을 흔드는 party
Watch us, we are the party shaking this game
보여줄게 확실한 safari
I'll show you a real safari
Badi badi, nobody can stop me
Body body, nobody can stop me
끼리끼리 봐봐
Birds of a feather, look at each other
Go, go, go, 빨리
Go, go, go, quickly
Acting on body
다들 벌써 멍하니
Everyone is already in a daze
멍하니
Dazed
Shake it off, what goes around
Shut your mouth, it will come back down
Ready to fight
Ready to scream
Abracadabra, let's go
Watch me, we bring it up
겁먹지 않는 눈짓
A fearless look
다 타버려, burn up in flames
Burn it all down, burn up in flames
Fierce as a demon
Believe in the beating
Just wait and see
We hit that high
Snake, snake, snake, come on now, don't be shy
Snake, snake, snake
뜨겁게 달아올라
Burning up hot
너와 나 어때, all day, all night
How about you and me, all day, all night
Hololive English, are you ready? Let's make it loud!
Yeah, we go hard!
We go hard!
Don't you ever try to pull me down, back off
We go hard
I want it all
Let's get it!
죽지 않아, 절대 안 꿇어
I won't die, I will never kneel
맞서 싸워, 시작이야
Fight back, this is the start
끝까지 달려가
Run all the way to the end
We'll hit that high!
Snake, snake, snake, come on now, don't be shy
Snake, snake, snake
같이 좀 맞춰 봐 이렇게
Let's match each other like this
멈출 수 없어, 같이 춤을 춰
Can't stop, let's dance together
We hit that high!
Don't be afraid of losing
It's just another beginning
Look at the cards we're dealing
Sometimes it takes a villain
Snake eyes, the time is nigh
Fly high with pride and leave your fears behind
Cut through the lies
This is the only battlefield I can televise
Ego is enormous, put the camera down and face it
They went and got complacent
Kill and run with me
You say you're standing for nothing, no one else can relate
Just know the company you keep is in the business of hate
Are you...
...afraid
Run away, I'm close to getting...
I've been dancing on my own in a bulletproof vest
Go on, shoot, shoot, shoot 'em up, baby, clear your mess
Ricochet, ricochet
You can think about me, I need time, I need time
Forget your street fights, this is trench war
I'll make you mosh, mosh, mosh till you hit the floor
Getting thirsty for collision, let them wonder what they're missing
in the front row
Now here we go
Draw a white line, it's a call to arms
Become the first hit, the unforgiven, make your decision
No fucking permission to riot, you got it rotten
Think about it for a second, identity, clean slate, now you're alone
メラメラ メラメラ
Mera mera, mera mera
Spin for nothing, play the coward, step on someone to devour
It's a sick twist, a mess we can't fix, yes
メラメラ メラメラ
Mera mera, mera mera
Spin for nothing, play the coward, step on someone to devour
It's a sick twist, a mess we can't fix, yes
手始めに、そう、これ
To begin with, yeah, this is it
WOAH!
さあ、目を瞑り この身に決めた
Now, close your eyes, I've resolved myself
角度を調整 角度微調整
Adjusting the angle, fine-tuning the angle
聞きなよBoy、身体揺らしなEvent
Listen up, boy, move your body in this event
Decider, Specialistがリードする
The decider and specialist will lead
Give me the beat, cheap shots, let it drop
We so fly, we don't know when to stop
I'm gonna show ya how we roll, how we roll, till we crack
Scythe-o, Scythe-o, Scythe-o
さあ、いざ行こう、勝つのは誰の番？
Now, let's go, whose turn is it to win?
集まったこの舞台でフィーバー！
Fever on this stage where we've gathered!
Slowly starving, 時間の無駄無駄、や、開始
Slowly starving, what a waste of time, alright, let's begin
I've been telling you not to fret
もう 息も絶え絶え 焦らす、急かす
Barely breathing, teasing, rushing
Dark night に刺さる 何者にもなるさ
Piercing the dark night, I will become someone
退屈な Lonely, Lonely trouble
Boring, lonely, lonely trouble
トラブルなどお構いなし、All block、踏み倒してやる
I don't care about trouble, I'll overrun all blocks
階段を上り 見下してやる
I'll climb the stairs and look down on you
A-WA, A-WA, A-WA, WOAH
Scream!
Scythe-o, Scythe-o, Scythe-o, Scythe-o
走り続けたらStop、ヤンデレセラーにsay yes
If you keep running, stop, say yes to the yandere seller
I can't play this, trust me, you are out of your league, child
I'm the one that's not impressed
手始めに、そう、これ
To begin with, yeah, this is it
敵陣に一人で殴り込み
Storming into the enemy territory alone
Fret...
We're not rivals
We're not equals
I gotta tell you
I never liked you
Now, would I lie to you?
Let me ignite you
Base instincts take control
Like primal ways of a warrior
Is it glory you're after, like me?
Underestimated everywhere I turn
Taking aim, but it doesn't make a difference at all
I got a million different enemies I cannot recall
You're rocking up to a battle when you know that you'll fall
Hidden motivation, watch it all burn
I gotta tell you
I never liked you
Now, would I lie to you?
Let me ignite you
When thunder crashes down
When the world caves under my pressure,
there'll be no one to save
Where is your pride, your human will to survive?
Was it just empty words for your grave?
I reach inside this soul
Now all that remains is delusion and decay
'Cause of you, I live this way
We're not rivals!
We're not equals!
Lately I realized I would never be, never be alone
It was always right in front of me
Do you know, do you remember, remember
How we used to be so carefree
...the rain wash over you
Still here...
Can you hear my heart like thunder?
Upside down 들리는 내 목소리
My voice echoing upside down...
I've got to make a move, make a move
So far I cannot break through the cage
And I, and I don't know how to reach to you
And I, and I don't know how to reach you.
Will I ever get a chance to speak out loud?
Or will it never be? Can't you feel it too?
Side by side we could laugh all through our days
Baby, just let me make my way
Glowing with soft and sudden sparks inside and out, they flare up
Glowing with soft and sudden sparks inside, and at night they flare up.
The moment we talk, all my secrets spilling over with talk
So when I step up to your side, my heart is beating in double-time
And every moment you make me feel alive, it goes like...
I can feel...
...the rain wash over you
Still here...
Can you hear my heart like thunder?
Upside down 들리는 내 목소리
My voice echoing upside down...
I've got to make a move, make a move
So far I cannot break through the cage
And I, and I don't know how to reach to you
And I, and I don't know how to reach you.
Will I ever get a chance to speak out loud?
Or will it never be? Can't you feel it too?
Side by side we could laugh all through our days
Baby, just let me make my way...
Will I ever get a chance to speak out loud?
Or will it never be? Can't you feel it too?
Side by side we could laugh all through our days
Baby, just let me make my way...
Hello! Hello!
Hello, hello, hello, hello, hello! Hi! Hello, hello.
Hello up there!
Hello down there!
Hello, everyone!
Hey, who are you?
Hi, darlings! This is Hololive English -Advent-'s Devilish Diva...
...the one, the only, Nerissa Ravencroft!
And with me...
Roses are red, the fire of my heart is blue,
also known as the Scarlet Queen, the Harbinger of Order, Leader of Justice...
I am Elizabeth Rose Bloodflame!
Lovely to see you, to see you, lovely!
That's so far! Yeah! That's so far!
Wow! What a setlist so far!
I know! We're starting out really strong!
We had...
Snake Eyes, Snake Eyes!
Woah! Oh my god!
And we had Mori...
rocking it out!
Seriously! And then Kronii coming in with her new song, so good!
Yeah, such cute dance moves!
And we had Advent and Justice, of course!
Yes, yes! Did you enjoy?
Did you enjoy?
Couldn't hear you, did you enjoy?!
Yeah, Hololive English is awesome!
Well, you know what? We didn't have solos yesterday.
No, no. So we must be having them today, right?
So excited!
Oh, yeah! For mine, I want to practice something, okay?
A little chant from Great Exardia.
So when I go "Oggy Oggy Oggy", you go "Oi Oi Oi!"
Are you ready?
Okay, here we go!
Oggy Oggy Oggy! Oi Oi Oi!
Perfect! Perfect! Kanpeki!
And you? Any sneak peeks about your solo?
Hmm, would you guys really like a sneak peek?
Well, I think I have to remind you all, no matter how you identify, no matter what you are, you in this audience today...
...are my wives! Can I hear it from my wives?!
What the freak! Everyone here is your wife?!
Including you!
So, if I ask you to sing along, you have to, all right?
You gotta!
Oh, yeah, that's my hint! Does it give it away? Maybe a little.
No, no, no, no, no, no!
You know, we're singing, and I was thinking that we...
I'd like to hear you guys sing, too.
You guys know I like harmonies!
Yes!
So we're going to split you into different notes, okay?
We have... you guys over here...
You guys over here...
And all of you... up!
So we're going to start off with you guys here.
We want you to hold this note...
Ah...
Perfect!
You guys: Ah...
Up there: Ah...
All right, everyone together!
Ah...
Woo! You did it! You did it!
Oh my god, we have a choir!
So good! We've got to do that more often, that was cool!
Yeah! I like hearing you all sing for us.
Hey, that reminds me of a song, doesn't it? You know that first note?
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
You know, something like... 3, 2, 1...
It's wondrous, somehow we met...
...along the way.
Now here you are...
...beside me...
...embracing Serendipity!
Wow, that was great, wasn't it?
Harmonizing, yeah!
It's wonderful harmonizing with you. And I just want to say thank you so much for being my friend.
I love you!
Anyway, we are going to sing together. We're going to sing together!
I got too excited! I got too excited!
I'm just too happy! I'm so happy!
Oh, look! Wee woo wee woo...
You got us!
Oh, I spammed too fast. There we go.
Anyway, 無料配信は、次の曲で...
Anyway, this next song will be the last...
...最後になります。
...for our free stream.
ライブの続きは、ぜひ配信チケットを買って見てね！
If you want to watch the rest of the live concert, please buy a stream ticket and watch!
The YouTube free sneak peek is only until the next song,
which is a duet!
If you want to continue watching,
click the link in the description and get your tickets now!
All right, everybody! After three, we all say "Serendipity", got it?
Aw, thank you so much. We love you guys so much! We love you!
All right, here we go! Three, two, one...
Serendipity!
Elizabeth Rose Bloodflame
Nerissa Ravencroft
Bloodraven
残酷な天使のように
Like a cruel angel,
少年よ 神話になれ
Young boy, become a legend!
蒼い風がいま 胸のドアを叩いても
Even if a blue wind knocks on the door to your heart right now,
私だけをただ見つめて 微笑んでるあなた
You just look at me and smile.
そっと触れるもの 求めることに夢中で
Obsessed with seeking out something gently touching you,
運命さえまだ知らない いたいけな瞳
With innocent eyes that don't even know fate yet.
だけどいつか気付くでしょう その背中には
But someday you'll probably realize that on your back,
遥か未来目指すための 羽根があること
You have wings to head for the far-off future.
残酷な天使のテーゼ
A cruel angel's thesis
窓辺からやがて飛び立つ
Will soon take flight through the window.
ほとばしる熱いパトスで
With surging, hot pathos,
思い出を裏切るなら
If you betray your memories...
この宇宙を抱いて輝く
Shine, holding the sky in your arms,
少年よ 神話になれ
young boy, become a legend!
ずっと眠ってる 私の愛の揺りかご
The cradle of my love has slept for so long...
あなただけが 夢の使者に 呼ばれる朝がくる
The morning will come when only you are summoned by a messenger of dreams.
細い首筋を 月あかりが映してる
The moonlight shines upon your slender neck.
世界中の時を止めて 閉じこめたいけど
I want to stop time across the world and lock you away, but...
もしもふたり逢えたことに 意味があるなら
If there is a meaning to the two of us meeting,
私はそう 自由を知る ためのバイブル
then I am, yes, the bible for learning freedom.
残酷な天使のテーゼ 悲しみがそしてはじまる
A cruel angel's thesis, and then sorrow begins...
抱きしめた命のかたち その夢に目覚めたとき
The moment you awaken to the dream of the form of life you embraced,
誰よりも光を放つ 少年よ 神話になれ
shining brighter than anyone else, young boy, become a legend!
人は愛をつむぎながら 歴史をつくる
People weave love together as they create history,
女神なんてなれないまま 私は生きる
and while unable to become a goddess, I will live on.
残酷な天使のテーゼ 窓辺からやがて飛び立つ
A cruel angel's thesis will eventually fly out from the window,
ほとばしる熱いパトスで 思い出を裏切るなら
if you betray your memories with an overflowing, burning pathos.
この宇宙を抱いて輝く
Shine, holding the sky in your arms,
少年よ 神話になれ
young boy, become a legend!
無料パートは終了いたしました。ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The sneak peek part of the show has ended. Thank you for watching.